Guide to the Records of Religious and Benevolent Societies, Organizations, and Meetings
Yale University Divinity School Library
- S
  - Sunday School Society (London), 1836, n.d. (Box 15)
  - Sunday School Society for Ireland, 1829, 1836-1837 (Box 15)
  - Sunday School Union (London), 1842, 1856 (Box 40)
  - Sunday School Union (New York), 1849, 1851 (Box 40)
  - Swedenborg Fellowship, 1896-1937, n.d. (Box 42)
    Place of Publication: New York Philadelphia Boston
    Subject Categories: Sects, religious societies Bible and tract societies
    Comments: AKA Swedenborg Foundation, Swedenborg Publishing Association, Swedenborgian Book Store, New Church Book Center
  - Systematic Beneficence Society, 1870-1875 (Box 42)
    SEE ALSO: American Systematic Beneficence Society and International, Christian Moral Science Association
- T-V
  - Temple of Truth, 1941 (Box 22)
  - Theosophical Society, 1890-1925, n.d. (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: United Kingdom United States India Cuba
  - Thirty-second Church Congress in the United States, 1914 Nov 3-6 (Box 24)
  - Tower Bible and Tract Society, 1894 (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: Allegheny, PA
    SEE ALSO: Watch Tower Bible and Tract Society
  - Tract Association of Friends, 1947, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Tract Association of the Society of Friends, 1838, 1840 (Box 43)
  - Trenton Female Tract Society, 1817 (Box 43)
  - Trinitarian Bible Society, 1832-1860, n.d. (Box 48)
  - Trinity Tract Society, n.d. (Box 43)
  - Ulster County Bible Society, 1861, 1874 (Box 15)
    Place of Publication: Kingston, NY
  - Ultimate Thought Society, 1925 (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: Detroit
  - Union Benevolent Association, 1800s (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: Philadelphia (?)
  - Union Gospel Mission, n.d. (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: St. Paul, MN
  - Union Maternal Association of Boston, 1882 (Box 43)
  - Union Pour la Vérité, 1909 (Box 43)
  - Union for Christian Work in the City of Brooklyn, 1884, 1890 (Box 16)
    Place of Publication: Brooklyn
  - Union for Home Work, 1873 (Box 43)
  - United Bible Societies
    SEE: International Conference of Bible Translators
  - United Campus Christian Fellowship, 1959 (Box 16)
  - United Committee (of Protestant Dissenters), 1827 (Box 43)
  - United Lodge of Theosophists, 1914 (Box 43)
  - United Society of Believers (Shakers), c.1880, 1936 (Box 54)
  - United Society of Christian Endeavor, 1885-1915, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Universal Brotherhood and Theosophical Society, 1909 (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: Point Loma, CA
  - Universal Christian Conference for Life and Work, 1921-1937 (Box 16)
    Place of Publication: New York London
    Box 16: Meeting minutes, 1921-1928; Stockholm conference, 1925; Box 17: Edinburgh conference, 1937
  - Universal Christian Conference for Life and Work (Box 17)
  - Universal Christian Council for Life and Work, 1931-1937 (Box 54)
    Council and Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1931-1936;American section, 1933-1942;Commission for Oecumenical Collaboration between Professors of Theology, 1933-1936; Other publications, 1934-1937
  - University Association, 1890s (Box 43)
    Comments: courses on world religions
  - University Christian Movement in the U.S.A., 1966 (Box 18)
  - University Commission on Race Questions, c.1919 (Box 22)
  - Urban Bishops Coalition, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Vedanta Centre, 1932 (Box 43)
  - Vegetarian Society, 1923 (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: Manchester, U.K.
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Sects, religious societies
  - Verein für Reformationsgeschichte, 1900 (Box 54)
    Place of Publication: Halle
  - Victoria Institute, or Philosophical Society of Great Britain, 1879, 1893 (Box 43)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Scholarly Societies
- W-Y
  - War Emergency Council on Student Christian Work, n.d. (Box 46)
  - Washington County Bible Society, 1875 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Marietta, OH
  - Watchtower Bible and Tract Society, 1898, 1904, 1913, 1931-1946 (Box 43)
    Place of Publication: Allegheny, PA Brooklyn, NY
    ALSO KNOWN AS: International Bible Students Association; SEE ALSO: Tower Bible and Tract Society
  - Weekly Tract Society, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Wesleyan-Methodist Sabbath and Week-day School Society for Darlington and its Vicinity, 1850 (Box 18)
    Place of Publication: Darlington, U.K.
  - West Lothian Bible Society, 1825 (Box 48)
  - Western Tract and Book Society (Box 44)
  - Westminster Trinitarian Bible Society, 1831 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Westminster
  - White Fund, 1937 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Clearwater, FL
  - Winona Assembly and Summer School Association, 1903 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Winona Lake, IN
  - Witness Committee, c.1923 (Box 44)
    Comments: re. proposed 19th amendment
  - Woman's National Sabbath Alliance, n.d. (Box 44)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; Sabbath observance
  - World Alliance for International Friendship Through the Churches, 1938 (Box 22)
  - World Conference for International Peace Through Religion, 1932 (Box 18)
  - World Conference on Faith and Order, 1913-1948 (Box 55)
    Preliminary Commissions, 1913-1920; Numbered series of publications, 1925-1936
  - World Conference on Faith and Order (Box 56)
    1937-1948; Miscellaneous publications of Continuation Committee, Secretariat, etc., 1921-1937
  - World Conference on Faith and Order (Box 57)
    Publications: 1938-1946
  - World Congress of Faiths, 1946 (Box 18)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Ecumenical movements
  - World Neighbors, 1980s (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Oklahoma City
  - World Wide Revival Prayer Movement, 1945 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Atlantic City, NJ
  - World's Christian Endeavor Union, 1942 (Box 46)
  - Wyclif Society, 1885-1911 (Box 54)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Scholarly societies
  - York Central Diocesan Society, 1829-1843 (Box 22)
    Place of Publication: York, U.K.
  - Young Men's Association for Mutual Improvement in the City of Albany, NY, 1835-1870 (Box 18)
  - Young Men's Bible Society of Cincinnati, 1841, 1855 (Box 48)
  - Young Men's Christian Union of New York, 1852 (Box 44)
  - Young Men's Education Society of New York and Brooklyn, 1827, 1846 (Box 18)
  - Young Men's New-York Bible Society, 1832-1833 (Box 48)
  - Young Men's Tract Society of Philadelphia, 1832 (Box 44)